Tonight at 11:00...
Doom!
Boy, that thing's big.
Fry, is my colossal eye
too big?
No, it's what
makes you you.
But it's so round,
so hideously round.
Leela, listen.
You're the most beautiful woman I've ever known.
Oh. So you only care
about my looks?
No, I... What?
Finally, New New York
got a blast of class today
as Nikolai, playboy ruler
of the Robo-Hungarian Empire,
arrived aboard his extravagant
caviar-powered yacht.
I am just
a humble emperor
with a big,
big crown!
Of course I'm not planning to steal that crown!
What?
True.
I've always dreamed
of being an emperor.
You know, for Halloween,
and then forever.
But heisting those jewels
would be difficult.
You'd be stupid to try.
I'll need accomplices.
A sexy vamp to distract
and tie up the guard.
Never!
A claw man to slip past
the metal detector
and cut the alarm wires.
Sorry, I'm set for life after that last job.
And finally, a chump,
to be caught on video
and later arrested.
As I told you on
Sucker-Punch Day,
I'm through being a chump.
Of course, it would all require
split-second robotic timing.
That's where I come in.
You see, I own a watch.
There. This time I'm sure
I've fixed the mind switcher.
Good, I'm sick of cleaning up
those heaps of dead monkeys.
But why would you want your mind in a new body?
Well, as a man
enters his 18th decade,
he thinks back on the mistakes he's made in life.
Like the heaps
of dead monkeys?
Science cannot move forward
without heaps!
No, what I regret is the
youth I wasted playing it safe.
I wasted my
youth porking out.
Yes, I remember.
Would you please
take that down?
It's making me hungry.
Funny, I could use a little
extra meat on my bones.
Wait a second!
If we switched bodies, I
could live life to the extreme,
and you could indulge
your demonic food lust.
We're just the people this mind
switcher was made for by us!
Wait, can I still
change my mind?
Let's find out.
It didn't work, you
doddering old...
Ah! Cartilage!
Dude, I bid you
a fond cowabunga.
I'm off to laugh
at the Reaper.
Look out, world,
here I...
I'm sorry, Amy, but your
body's not up to the task.
Also, I don't care for these
boobs flapping every which way.
Now, quit your
bologna-gargling
and let's switch back
into our original bodies.
Body-switching, eh?
Mayhap the heist is back on.
Who needs accomplices, if I
can just use their bodies?
Professor,
what's not happening?
Bad news, me.
I failed to take into account
the cerebral immune response.
You idiot!
Once two bodies
have switched minds,
they can never
switch back.
However,
perhaps they can.
Maybe we can swap back
using a third body
for temporary storage space.
I'm 60% storage space.
You are?
I... Mmm?
Well, I'm off to
the royal yacht
for a quick
seduce-and-snatch.
See you!
Now, then, Amy
we'll simply switch bodies,
and then we'll...
We'll...
No, I'd be back
in my body,
but then you and Bender
would be switched.
And the Amy and Bender bodies can't
trade minds again, since they just did.
Oh, no!
Is it possible to
get everyone back
to normal using
four or more bodies?
I'm not sure.
I'm afraid we need to use
math.
Stupid air-needing lungs.
The crown jewels.
Now I just have to locate
the guard and seduce him in...
Four seconds?
Who goes there?
Three, two, one.
Hello, big boy.
Silence!
I am Basil,
the Emperor's cousin
and chief of his royal guard.
And I shall not
be seduced by a...
I said...
Professor?
What's the matter?
I'm Amy. The Professor and I switched bodies.
Oh, lord.
All I wanted was to
gorge myself a little,
but I can't digest anything
with these false teeth
and this hit-or-miss colon.
At least you get a senior discount at the movies.
I hate paying $14 to see
Nicolas Cage solve things.
If you want to save $2,
we could switch bodies.
Hmm. We can always
switch back, right?
Hey, Leela.
Mmm.
What smells saturated?
Deep-fried ice cream sandwich wrapped
in frosting and lightly baconed.
Whoa. That sounds like
something Amy would say and eat.
I am Amy. Leela and I used the
Professor's mind-switching machine.
So Leela's
in your body?
Not exactly.
Aha! You do only
like me for my body!
That is entirely
not true, sir!
Now to go switch bodies with
Zoidberg, sneak past the metal detector
and clip the alarm wires,
all in less than...
Ten minutes ago? Oh!
Uh, could you come back
when my chump gets here?
Now, then, what is a filthy human
doing aboard my royal yacht?
With all due respect, Your
Majesty, I'm a robot like you.
I just switched bodies
with some bimbo.
Go ahead, ask me something
only a robot would know.
A reverse Turing Test, eh?
Very good.
What is the square root
of nine?
Uh, hold on, let me
just get out a pencil.
Okay, look, I'm not that kind of
robot. I'm more this kind of robot.
He steps forwards
but moves backwards.
By the gods!
He is a machine!
No, that won't
restore everyone, either.
Besides, I don't want
my decrepit old body back!
I'm running away with this invincible
robot body and joining something.
Look, I paid for 15 robot
clowns per cubic meter of car,
and you're barely giving me 12.
Now, crumple up and get in...
And fasten your seatbelts.
Come on!
Good day.
I am Nonchalanto,
the robot daredevil.
And my dream is to risk my life
in strange and original ways.
Hmm. You don't look
so foolhardy to me.
That's the dumbest thing
anybody's ever done.
You're hired!
So you're a common
bending robot,
with a human
peasant roommate?
Oh, crap,
that is what I am!
No, Bender, I envy you.
I'm so bored with all these pretentious trappings.
The jewels, the parties,
the beautiful robo-women.
Hello.
My fiancйe,
Princess Flavia.
Dearest, meet Bender. He's a robot in
the body of a Chinese Martian physicist.
How tedious.
Oh, to escape this
gilded cage for a day.
You know,
we could trade bodies.
I could take over
the humdrum royal stuff,
and you could be
a regular Joe for a day.
Or more. Much more.
In that horrid non-robot body
? Sir, I have my standards.
Ah, but what if I could put you
in my fabulous bending-robot body?
Me, posing
as a lowly bending unit?
How wicked!
But wait, I'm supposed to give
a speech at the U. N. tomorrow.
Can I trust you to do it?
You can trust anything.
So now Leela's
all crotchety
because she thinks I'm not attracted
to her in the Professor's body.
You aren't, are you?
Of course not!
But I was willing to lie about
it. What more can a man do?
A man can give her a toke
of her own medicine.
Yes! I could put my mind
into a hideous body
and show Leela she's
not attracted to me.
But it would have to be a
really, really disgusting body.
Friends! Friends! I've
got barnacles on my tuchus.
The long search is over.
Wait here and earn interest
while I find my robot body.
Professor?
Leela. Amy?
Bender.
Have you seen my body?
I think
the Professor's in it.
Yeah, he said something
about running away.
Then he ran away.
What? Whither?
What am I gonna do?
I got an emperor all patsied up to switch bodies,
but only with
another robot!
Washbucket full.
Scruffy's work here
is done.
Now to find Emperor
Von Richendoof.
Now to find Scruffy.
Switch bodies?
I don't see why not.
I also don't see why.
In your face, Leela.
If you're a bender, why is
your body full of fetid water?
If you're an emperor,
why don't you shut up?
Move it, Fry!
Well, so long.
Wait!
Point me to my
normal human roommate!
That's him there.
Maybe.
Got to go!
Robot?
Yes, 'tis I, Bender.
Do you not recognize
your own best friend?
Aha! The guy in this body
has a friend!
Bender, old pal!
It's me, the Fry!
But then Nicolas Cage discovered
the real treasure was his family.
Yes, I'll hold.
Hey, Leela, look!
I'm in Zoidberg!
Fry?
You're not so shallow
that you find me repulsive
because of my body, are you?
Not at all.
Amy? Stop it!
Fry, help! She's turning me into a parade float.
Ew! Look at her!
Oh. So you're so shallow
that my body disgusts you
if it puts on
a little extra weight?
That wasn't
a little extra weight.
Admit it! You don't care
about the inner me at all!
No, you admit it!
You'd be ashamed
to be seen in public
with someone as
hideous as me!
Would not!
Oh, yeah?
Then I challenge you to a
romantic dinner at Elzar's tonight.
It's on.
Sweet orca of Majorca!
You make Fat Albert look
like Normal Albert!
I don't know what to do.
Do you think I
should eat more butter?
I am putting a stop
to this right now!
Come on.
We're switching bodies.
Hermes, no!
I'll ruin your body, too!
Three decades of the munchies
beat you to it.
You make
quite a show, young man.
You remind me of myself
as a young cannon.
Big Bertha is
the circus's grande dame.
She shoots robots
through the air.
Excuse me.
Too much goulash.
I've always wanted
to be shot out of something.
How about a quick
blast after lunch?
Alas, a fine big one like you
would shatter my barrel.
But, ah, to amaze
the crowd once more.
I understand
the problems of age,
but suppose I could
put you in a new body?
Never! My body may be old,
but it is mine,
and every crack a memory of
heavy things shot a long way.
Good day!
I have everything I ever
wanted. Money, wealth, riches.
Yet something's missing.
A hot princess with
whom to get grizzly.
Hello.
Hello, baby!
Huh? Hey,
what's going on here?
And why are you kissing my
dashing cousin instead of me?
Nikolai,
you imperial fool.
We've been having
an affair for 700 years.
At long last, I shall kill you, blame the burglar
and inherit the throne.
Farewell, Nikolai.
Wait! I'm not Nikolai!
I'm Bender, the fabulous body-switching burglar.
So you are. However, you do have Nikolai's body,
and that's the part
we want to kill.
Great food, huh?
Ew!
I'm sorry, Leela.
I hope that didn't make you
ashamed to be seen with me.
No, it only makes
you more attractive.
Ew!
Oh! Did my bodily
infirmity embarrass you?
Not at all.
It's just another thing that
makes you a very special lady.
You mean, like my penis?
Admit it!
You're disgusted by me!
No,
you're disgusted by me!
I'm as attracted to
you as I've ever been!
Prove it!
Well, Bender, here's our apartment
that we live in every day.
A floor?
We live like kings!
Kings? Silence!
Like you, I'm a common lout.
Now fetch me some
working-class cognac
from our brandy storeroom
that you know how to find.
Uh...
Relax, Bender.
I'll dry up that leak
with this heating box.
Ah, cigars.
Light me up, old friend.
There you are,
Emperor Nikolai.
It's time for your
speech to the U. N.
What now?
Miss Wong?
No, Scruffy,
I am Washbucket.
I love you. Washbucket has always loved you.
This is wrong, Washbucket.
Oh, it would be
sweet for a while,
but in the back of our minds,
we'd know that I'm a man
and you're
janitorial equipment.
In another city,
we could be anyone we want!
Go. Go now,
before I beg you to stay.
Yep.
Please welcome an insane
dictator, and one heck of a bowler,
Emperor Nikolai!
Thanks, Nixon.
How we doing?
I love you,
Your Majesty!
Shut up, Madame Ambassador!
I know it!
Anyhow,
I'd now like to digress
from my prepared remarks
to say I'm done!
Ladies and gentlemen,
this robot is an impostor!
I shall enjoy this.
Not me!
That devil, Basil,
will kill our emperor.
You're Robo-Hungarian?
Yes. Our nation's
chief export is carnies.
If only there were some way I
could get to the U. N. to help.
There is.
Get in, Nonchalanto.
Bertha, no!
It would kill you!
I have not so much
time left anyhow.
But you could get a new body!
You could have a rich, full life!
I am trying to have
a rich, full life!
Long live Robo-Hungary!
Me!
Thank God you've come!
This is for Big Bertha!
That is not what I meant
to give you for Big Bertha.
That was nice.
Oh, yeah.
Ow! Ow!
Whoever you are, you're the
bravest robot I've ever seen.
I like killing brave things.
Good! Because I've got
20 of them per cubic meter.
When I grow up,
I want to be a diplomat!
Well, if there's one thing
I've learned, it's a lesson.
I believe this
belongs to you.
I shall sell it to
help the common folk,
now that I understand
their misery.
Yeah, good luck with that.
I must say, Hermes, you've
got a smoking-hot body.
I was inspired by Amy.
Wow! How'd you do it?
Well,
there I was at Elzar's,
eating a nice pork sundae,
and suddenly,
I just lost my appetite.
Forever.
Q to the E to the D!
So it is possible for us all to
get back to our original bodies?
Stone-cold munching, Prof.
Sweet Clyde, characterize your inversion theorem.
Basically, no matter how
permuted-up your minds are,
they can be restored using,
at most, two extra players.
And they say pure math has
no real-world applications!
Everybody back
in their zones?
Yes sir!
Yes!
Ah! My body may be old,
but it is mine.
Brilliant work, Clyde!
You'll win the NBA's highest
academic honor for this.
Also,
I'm making you a duke.
So long, filthy commoners!
Ў Adiуs!
And I'm left with the real jewels safely inside...
His compartment?
All right.
I'll need accomplices.